[Music]
hello friends i hope you're doing well
and taking care of yourself
this week i'm starting my new temporary
job as a bookseller and i'm so excited
it has really sunk in that my life will
be very different next year possibly in
a new home
much of the last four years i've spent
living alone in various places sometimes
by choice other times because i felt i
had nowhere to go
thankfully i've always had some friends
or family nearby but i've still found
myself for the most part embracing a
quiet life predominantly spent my own
company and on my own terms
at least the time i had away from work
it is a slower sword of life mostly
nature walks and cups of tea and reading
books not too much rash or excitement
but i would say experiencing an
overarching contentedness with what
daily life has offered me
[Music]
to start cultivating that feeling i
realized i needed to heal the
relationship i had with both my inner
self but also my physical body
this was absolutely crucial to me when
years ago i was recovering from an
eating disorder and trying to develop a
more positive relationship with myself i
remember for a long time i didn't even
use social media because for some reason
i kept being recommended plastic surgery
advertisements let me know if this
happened to you at some point because i
felt like i was being haunted
and disturbingly many of these surgery
examples seem to be designed to change
common ethnic features that i happen to
share with my mother's side of my family
my larger more protruding and curved
nose comes to mind something that i have
grown to love and be very content with
but that wasn't always the case
i also had severe cystic acne which is a
type of skin condition that's extremely
painful sometimes my face would be so
swollen i couldn't open my eyes properly
as someone who was quite fragile and
insecure about those very things when
they were younger as many women are
socialized to be
it was definitely a sign i needed to
unplug for a while until i was in a
better place
[Music]
do
so cute
[Music]
so
through stepping away from those
influences at a key point in my life i
decided to try to form a more
independent definition of beauty
something far more inclusive than what i
held before it is no longer reliant on
weight on looking a certain way i can
now admire the unique features of others
while valuing my own i still don't feel
comfortable in my skin every day but i
think it's important to know that that's
normal
our emotions inevitably change we cannot
be happy every moment of our lives
neither should we believe difficult
moments will last forever i now look at
the change of seasons of the moon cycles
and all cycles of life and death as
evidence that what i feel today will
inevitably evolve into something else
and i can choose to believe things can
and will get better in time
i've had my ups and downs this year but
i've kept making progress
[Music]
so
recovering from issues with your mind
and body relationship takes so much time
and for me there was a spiritual
component i had to resolve as well
as for practical measures i covered my
mirrors for a while permanently
throughout my scale didn't buy new
clothes or do anything focused at all in
my body and external self i read books
on the topic and threw myself into new
hobbies and interests i started hiking
and instead appreciating what my body
could do for me not how it looked
in my case that was incredibly healing
and while everyone's journey to
self-love is different i definitely
think there's always value in finding
new passions and getting creative with
how you spend your time
when i put value in things separate from
my insecurities over time it took power
away from them
i'm still on that journey and i've
struggled at times to maintain my health
and through that i've realized how
important it is not to expect perfection
from ourselves
to recognize the power of your own voice
to have courage in the face of a world
that is so scary at times to see a seed
of something beautiful inside each of us
[Music]
do
okay
hello everyone i hope you're all having
a wonderful day
it's been an interesting week over here
there's usually been snow in the morning
because it snows overnight and then it
all melts away by the end of the day so
it's been kind of chaotic weather so
i've been enjoying it though i
i am always amazed every time the snow
comes for the first time because
it is so magical just to see everything
turn white kind of mysteriously while
i'm asleep it's it's really
it's just really beautiful it's um
a very
spiritual time if that makes any sense
it's always kind of this really
interesting experience to
walk through the snow and just be quiet
and even the animals seem to be reverent
during the first snowfall you know
everything is just so quiet
the event of the week has been that my
dog broke his tooth
which if you have a labrador let me know
if you also have this problem but when
i throw for him he runs full speed
in the direction of the frisbee but he
doesn't look where he's going so he
starts running while still looking at
you
and he runs into things just smacks full
speed and um he smacked into a rock and
he
broke his tooth and
he doesn't care at all i didn't even
notice until later i was uh clipping his
toenails and i looked and i saw that the
the nerve was exposed and it seemed like
it would normally be quite painful but
he apparently has
no sense of pain so he couldn't care
less but i wanted to bring him to the
veterinarian
and have him checked out so i don't know
if his tooth will need to be pulled or
capped mr darcy also loves this time of
year i like to put him in the garden
when it's not snowing and he eats all
the little leftover dead plants and he
frolics and he just has such a good time
so yeah it's wonderful i i don't know if
you guys i
i think i mentioned this before but
mr darcy is a senior he's a really
really old rabbit and i personally think
he looks very well for his age and is
aged very gracefully but he is very very
old and so i do get a little worried
about him in the winter because he does
need to spend a little more time than
usual indoors and he just loves being
outside and i think it really keeps him
very youthful and very healthy
this time of year my fiance and i try to
watch a lot of
movies more than usual because we tend
to be
inside because it gets dark so early so
if you have any good movie
recommendations please let me know
we have been enjoying a lot of them
recently we just watched them
hunt for the wilder people not too long
ago and we really really liked it it was
really funny so
yeah if you have any recommendations
please let me know i'm open to
pretty much all types of movies except
very scary ones i am
a total baby so
now that i've been enjoying snow in the
mornings i've been rereading some of my
favorite books and so i recently reread
the snow child by eowyn ivey and she
came out with another book called the
bright edge of the world
that i just started rereading recently
and
it's very very interesting it's based
off a
true story
of a expedition in alaska and it's it's
fascinating it's very different from her
first book but i've been enjoying that
as well i'm just mentioning that because
um i had some people reach out wondering
what i was reading lately and so i have
to admit i've been rereading a lot of my
favorite books so if you have any
recommendations please let me know thank
you everyone for the really sweet
comments on my last video it's been
really exciting to think about the
prospect of having a home it's
terrifying buying a home
it's
you know the financial part of it can
sometimes be
intimidating and so i've been you know
my fiance and i've been kind of learning
and understanding all that better to
make sure we're prepared and so we're
very excited so hopefully i can give you
an update on all that soon but it will
be at least a couple months before i can
give out more information about what's
going on there so but i'm really excited
so thank you all for your well wishes
and i will let you know what happens
with all that anyway i hope you all have
a wonderful day and that you stay safe
and you stay warm if you're in a cold
area like this and if you're in a nice
warm area you can know that i really
wish i was there right now so
anyway have a wonderful evening or
morning wherever you are in your day
right now and i will see you next week
goodbye
[Music]
so i was trying to show
you guys how i use food coloring to
paint designs on cookies
and i just started and i went to go get
some water
and i came back to this which
i found really weird
i wonder what happened